The next variation of a vest that you can design, or that you can build on, as far as your design process goes, and again, all this stuff is for you to just try.
Don't take my ideas literally, because what I'm doing now, and don't take them as who I am as a designer, either.
I need to say that, because they're just shapes for you to build on. I'm doing the most basic and elementary things that I can think of, that give my concept a way of establishing itself in your head, and then letting you build on that concept.
This is a shrunken sweater vest with ribbing.
Everybody knows what that is.
It's going to hit to be shrunken, and needs to hit above, above the hips.
It needs to hit above the waist typically, or right at the waist.
That's technically shrunken.
If it hits a little bit below the waist, well, you just don't need to try it, because it shrinks.
There's not really a term for that.
It's just too short for being long, and too long for being shrunken.
Shrunken is just shrunken all around.
Ribbing, you know what a ribbing is, knit contrast to the regular knit that's there.